<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Tokyo Hacker Girls</title><link>https://blog.thgirls.yt/</link><description>Recent content on Tokyo Hacker Girls</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.thgirls.yt/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Glass Door 15</title><link>https://blog.thgirls.yt/p/2024/11/the-glass-door-15/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.thgirls.yt/p/2024/11/the-glass-door-15/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://blog.thgirls.yt/p/2024/11/the-glass-door-15/blue.jpg" alt="Featured image of post The Glass Door 15" />&lt;p>Afterword 01&lt;/p>
&lt;p>After our beach treasure hunt, Uncle, Auntie, and I went to a seaside café to relax and chat.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>And no, it wasn’t just because I didn’t want to use the beach restroom. 🙄&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I ordered a cola, and as we talked, I told them how, here, I’d never felt my soul so light. The food didn’t rely on heavy oils, salts, and sugar to spike my dopamine; both my body and mind felt so much more agile. Even sneaking a bowl of instant noodles one day left me feeling salty and sluggish all day. Uncle and Auntie laughed, delighted to hear me say this.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>We talked about so many things. I told them that this was the happiest vacation of my life. I paint, I sing, and I’m with people I love—it’s too good to be true. They said it’s rare to meet someone who loves both science and art, and I laughed, saying I never really loved science or programming. As a kid, I won roomfuls of art awards, only to be forced to give it up in favor of math competitions. Music, too, was dismissed as a frivolous distraction. I told them how, in Asian families, parents always say that chasing your passion will only leave you homeless.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>They looked at me as if I were from another planet.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I laughed and held out my right hand, showing them one of my finger. They asked about the thick callus there. I said it was from all the homework I used to do as a kid.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>They looked at me like I was an alien again.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I shrugged. “It’s normal—every Asian kid has one.” We had to memorize countless classical poems, formulas and English words. Each day, teachers and class leaders would randomly quiz us, and during exams, we’d have to write it all out. If we couldn’t, we’d be punished with standing, extra assignments, or even a slap on the wrist.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>It’s so different from Western education, with its emphasis on critical thinking, on valuing the individual. They looked at me as though I’d been mistreated, but I assured them, “It’s like that for everyone. Without comparison, there’s no pain.”&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Had I never left to see the world beyond, I might have rationalized that rigid system and imposed it on my own children.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I looked out over the distant ocean. Suddenly, I understood why monks and poets like Tao Yuanming withdrew from society to create their own peaceful refuges.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The human world is hardly a place for life’s true joys. More and more, it’s turning everyone to masters and servants.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>To seek true love in this world, you have to escape its clutches, flee as far as you can.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I spent my life twisting and contorting myself into the image my parents once dreamed of, only to realize I had never truly lived for myself.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>This wild European sea is my own Peach Blossom Spring, my refuge.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Finally, I can stop being who others want me to be—I will do what I love, love who I choose, rebel against every voice that denies true love, and shout my own truths by the sea with every bit of strength I have.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Even if to others, I’m young, foolish, and tragic.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Even if they want to cover my mouth and drag me down into their dreamless sleep.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Because I know, in my life’s brightest and darkest moments, countless words and songs of love have poured into my soul. They planted a seed of courage, guiding me forward, waiting for me to become someone who helps others chase their dreams.&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>That day, Miss Lin looked over at me in bed and said, “I think I’ve realized something.”&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I asked her what she’d discovered.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Miss Lin said, “When my dad was pursuing my mom, he went after her, wholeheartedly, time and time again.”&lt;/p>
&lt;p>She paused, then added, “Maybe that’s why, when I invited you to do that public talk about the Apple vulnerability, I somehow knew you would eventually believe yourself and say yes, even after you turned it down again and again. I carried my father’s courage with me, hoping you’d see my sincerity. That courage brought us here—to this happy future we’re living.”&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I laughed. I realized that this was Miss Lin’s own gift to me, her own apple of fate, passed down through her parents’ love.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>And an apple—that’s the reward for those who commit themselves to love.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>【Cyan's Picks】2024 Black Friday Tech Recommendations 🩵✨</title><link>https://blog.thgirls.yt/p/2024/11/guide/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.thgirls.yt/p/2024/11/guide/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://blog.thgirls.yt/p/2024/11/guide/mac.jpg" alt="Featured image of post 【Cyan's Picks】2024 Black Friday Tech Recommendations 🩵✨" />&lt;h1 id="2024-black-friday-tech-recommendations">2024 Black Friday Tech Recommendations
&lt;/h1>&lt;h2 id="hi-there-cyber-wonders">Hi there, Cyber Wonders
&lt;/h2>&lt;p>It’s Black Friday again! Today, I’m sharing some of my all-time favorite tech products that have genuinely improved my quality of life and boosted my happiness.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="about-me">About Me
&lt;/h3>&lt;p>Hi, I am Cyan! I’m a aspiring anime artist and singer, with over a decade of experience as a coding enthusiast. For the past few years, I worked for Google in North America, and in my spare time, I run a YouTube channel filled with gaming, covers, videos, and live streams. I’m also the fiancée of Asahi Lina, a Linux kernel developer for Asahi Linux. These recommendations are treasures that have greatly helped us in work efficiency, creative endeavors, and relaxation.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Let’s dive right in!&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.thgirls.yt/p/2024/11/guide/mac.jpg"
width="6000"
height="4000"
srcset="https://blog.thgirls.yt/p/2024/11/guide/mac_hu17905334356599523177.jpg 480w, https://blog.thgirls.yt/p/2024/11/guide/mac_hu8297502978819107430.jpg 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="MacBook"
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="150"
data-flex-basis="360px"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="1-macbook-air--macbook-pro-for-everyone">&lt;strong>1. MacBook Air / MacBook Pro (For Everyone)&lt;/strong>
&lt;/h3>&lt;ul>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Why I Recommend It&lt;/strong>: MacBooks have been my go-to machine for college, grad school, and work at Google. They’re fantastic for coding, drawing, and recording. My 2014 MacBook Air lasted me seven years before I upgraded to a Pro, which handles video editing, Minecraft, VTube Studio, and streaming like a champ. Both the M1 and M2 models now support Asahi Linux, with M3 and M4 support in the future. Air does great for most people. Need performance for video editing, AI training, or intensive coding tasks? Grab the Pro.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;a class="link" href="https://www.dealmoon.com/en/round-up-amazon-apple-device/3434717.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Check it out&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.thgirls.yt/p/2024/11/guide/ipad.jpg"
width="3151"
height="1913"
srcset="https://blog.thgirls.yt/p/2024/11/guide/ipad_hu7958596230205701419.jpg 480w, https://blog.thgirls.yt/p/2024/11/guide/ipad_hu17776037565444788723.jpg 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="iPad"
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="164"
data-flex-basis="395px"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="2-ipad-for-students-artists-and-media-creators">&lt;strong>2. iPad (For Students, Artists, and Media Creators)&lt;/strong>
&lt;/h3>&lt;ul>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Why I Recommend It&lt;/strong>: It’s a perfect blend of work and play. Add a keyboard, and it’s almost like a mini computer. For someone like me who loves taking notes and drawing, paired with the Apple Pencil and a paper-like screen protector, it feels like a digital notebook/sketchbook that can be archived. It’s also my main tool for creating anime-style art. While I don’t recommend iPads as a primary coding device for CS students—SSH over school networks can be unreliable—it’s a fantastic secondary productivity tool.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Black Friday Deal&lt;/strong>: Save $100–$200&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;a class="link" href="https://www.dealmoon.com/en/round-up-amazon-apple-device/3434717.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Check it out&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.thgirls.yt/p/2024/11/guide/alienware.jpg"
width="1920"
height="1080"
srcset="https://blog.thgirls.yt/p/2024/11/guide/alienware_hu13437777717584247200.jpg 480w, https://blog.thgirls.yt/p/2024/11/guide/alienware_hu16293939087178167160.jpg 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="Alienware"
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="177"
data-flex-basis="426px"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="3-alienware-gaming-desktop">&lt;strong>3. Alienware Gaming Desktop&lt;/strong>
&lt;/h3>&lt;ul>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Why I Recommend It&lt;/strong>: This was my first streaming machine. It’s not the cheapest, but it’s reliable out of the box. OBS streaming is seamless, and it handles graphics-heavy games like Cyberpunk 2077 (with 4080/4090 GPUs) effortlessly. If you have the budget and want a pre-built desktop, this is it.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;a class="link" href="https://m.dealmoon.com/en/round-up-dell-black-friday-sale/3171307.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Check it out&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.thgirls.yt/p/2024/11/guide/watch.jpg"
width="6040"
height="3186"
srcset="https://blog.thgirls.yt/p/2024/11/guide/watch_hu15100681936727141382.jpg 480w, https://blog.thgirls.yt/p/2024/11/guide/watch_hu4717220343303309476.jpg 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="Apple Watch"
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="189"
data-flex-basis="454px"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="4-apple-watch-series-10">&lt;strong>4. Apple Watch Series 10&lt;/strong>
&lt;/h3>&lt;ul>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Why I Recommend It&lt;/strong>: I got this for health reasons and its integration with the Apple ecosystem. It monitors heart rate, sleep, and a few potentially life-saving features. My favorite part is the Walkie-Talkie feature. It’s like having a private intercom system at home. Make sure to try different bands; rubber ones may cause irritation if worn for too long.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Black Friday Deal&lt;/strong>: $379 (Rose Gold)&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;a class="link" href="https://m.dealmoon.com/en/379-apple-watch-series-10-gps-46mm-case/4588327.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Check it out&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.thgirls.yt/p/2024/11/guide/herman.jpg"
width="6000"
height="4000"
srcset="https://blog.thgirls.yt/p/2024/11/guide/herman_hu18042779437952700527.jpg 480w, https://blog.thgirls.yt/p/2024/11/guide/herman_hu13927083726223164588.jpg 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="Herman Miller Chair"
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="150"
data-flex-basis="360px"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="5-herman-miller-ergonomic-chair">&lt;strong>5. Herman Miller Ergonomic Chair&lt;/strong>
&lt;/h3>&lt;ul>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Why I Recommend It&lt;/strong>: Sitting properly is crucial for health. After my father underwent a life-threatening surgery due to poor posture, I realized how important a good chair is. I’ve tried gaming chairs, kneeling chairs, IKEA’s MARKUS, and more, but Herman Miller chairs are the only ones that keep my back pain-free for hours. They’re pricey, but they’re worth it for those who work long hours. Pro tip: Check secondhand markets for great deals! The second-hand chairs from big companies are usually much cheaper and really good for your back.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Black Friday Deal&lt;/strong>: 15%–25% off&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;a class="link" href="https://store.hermanmiller.com/holiday-sale/constant/ergonomic-office-chairs-hm_gaming-chairs_office-stools_task-chairs" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Check it out&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.thgirls.yt/p/2024/11/guide/airpod.jpg"
width="5568"
height="3712"
srcset="https://blog.thgirls.yt/p/2024/11/guide/airpod_hu8590561627159077593.jpg 480w, https://blog.thgirls.yt/p/2024/11/guide/airpod_hu1966295132748977787.jpg 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="AirPods Pro"
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="150"
data-flex-basis="360px"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="6-airpods-pro">&lt;strong>6. AirPods Pro&lt;/strong>
&lt;/h3>&lt;ul>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Why I Recommend It&lt;/strong>: These are my most essential tools. From music playback and Siri interactions to ASMR meditations at night, they’re perfect. While the regular AirPods can easily fall out during sleep, the Pro model is much more secure and comfortable for extended wear.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Black Friday Deal&lt;/strong>: $169.99 ($80 off)&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;a class="link" href="https://www.dealmoon.com/en/168-apple-airpods-pro-2nd-generation/4513916.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Check it out&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.thgirls.yt/p/2024/11/guide/tag.jpg"
width="8256"
height="5504"
srcset="https://blog.thgirls.yt/p/2024/11/guide/tag_hu8739394924672680522.jpg 480w, https://blog.thgirls.yt/p/2024/11/guide/tag_hu17694714306514011027.jpg 1024w"
loading="lazy"
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="150"
data-flex-basis="360px"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="7-airtag">&lt;strong>7. AirTag&lt;/strong>
&lt;/h3>&lt;ul>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Why I Recommend It&lt;/strong>: I have around 12 of these at home—they’re just that useful! Each pet gets one on their collar, and thanks to the “Find My” feature, I’ve recovered my runaway cats and dogs countless times. They can literally be life-saving. They’re also great for tracking wallets, purses, bags, keys, and more. Remember, the batteries will need replacing eventually. Creators, beware of receiving gifts with hidden trackers inside. When traveling, stay vigilant for unknown AirTags—you’ll receive an alert on your iPhone if one is near.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Black Friday Deal&lt;/strong>: 4-pack for just $72.99&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;a class="link" href="https://m.dealmoon.com/en/69-apple-airtag-4-pack/4587103.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Check it out&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.thgirls.yt/p/2024/11/guide/insta.jpg"
width="2048"
height="1536"
srcset="https://blog.thgirls.yt/p/2024/11/guide/insta_hu11225099745840004979.jpg 480w, https://blog.thgirls.yt/p/2024/11/guide/insta_hu9294070068517644603.jpg 1024w"
loading="lazy"
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="133"
data-flex-basis="320px"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="8-fujifilm-instax-mini-12-instant-camera">&lt;strong>8. Fujifilm Instax Mini 12 Instant Camera&lt;/strong>
&lt;/h3>&lt;ul>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Why I Recommend It&lt;/strong>: Why bother with an instant camera in the smartphone age? Because physical photos carry so many memories. Clip them onto a string and create a photo wall—super romantic!&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Black Friday Deal&lt;/strong>: Bundle for just $69.99&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;a class="link" href="https://m.dealmoon.com/en/mini-11-for-59-fujifilm-instax/4608439.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Check it out&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.thgirls.yt/p/2024/11/guide/deck.jpg"
width="2400"
height="1350"
srcset="https://blog.thgirls.yt/p/2024/11/guide/deck_hu1099061869459116799.jpg 480w, https://blog.thgirls.yt/p/2024/11/guide/deck_hu6651449341479245955.jpg 1024w"
loading="lazy"
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="177"
data-flex-basis="426px"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="9-steam-deck-oled-1tb">&lt;strong>9. Steam Deck OLED 1TB&lt;/strong>
&lt;/h3>&lt;ul>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Why I Recommend It&lt;/strong>: White! Arch Linux! A must-have!&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Black Friday Deal&lt;/strong>: $679&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;a class="link" href="https://m.dealmoon.com/en/679-00-steam-deck-oled-limited-edition-white/4605413.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Check it out&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.thgirls.yt/p/2024/11/guide/yeti.jpg"
width="7008"
height="4672"
srcset="https://blog.thgirls.yt/p/2024/11/guide/yeti_hu467729054312165313.jpg 480w, https://blog.thgirls.yt/p/2024/11/guide/yeti_hu9327084780446190915.jpg 1024w"
loading="lazy"
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="150"
data-flex-basis="360px"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="10-blue-yeti-usb-microphone">&lt;strong>10. Blue Yeti USB Microphone&lt;/strong>
&lt;/h3>&lt;ul>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Why I Recommend It&lt;/strong>: This was my first streaming mic, and it’s perfect for beginners—easy to use with great quality. Show up to a work Zoom standup with this beast, and everyone will compliment your professional sound. “Are you a YouTuber?” they’ll ask. Instant icebreaker, and you’re suddenly the team favorite. According to Lina though, with good audio processing, cheaper microphones are also great - like the ones we use in Europe, Behringer Ultravoice.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Black Friday Deal&lt;/strong>: Just $76.49&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;a class="link" href="https://m.dealmoon.com/en/84-logitech-for-creators-blue-yeti-usb-microphone-for-pc/4582940.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Check it out&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.thgirls.yt/p/2024/11/guide/standing.jpg"
width="4415"
height="3311"
srcset="https://blog.thgirls.yt/p/2024/11/guide/standing_hu4200355733989190403.jpg 480w, https://blog.thgirls.yt/p/2024/11/guide/standing_hu12154874027613087746.jpg 1024w"
loading="lazy"
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="133"
data-flex-basis="320px"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="11-standing-desk">&lt;strong>11. Standing Desk&lt;/strong>
&lt;/h3>&lt;ul>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Why I Recommend It&lt;/strong>: Sitting too long? Stand for a while! Bonus points if you add a treadmill underneath. If you’re on a budget, IKEA lets you customize your own desktop. Lina loves hers, but you’ll need to manage the cables underneath carefully—otherwise, a spilled drink could be disastrous. Our cats were initially curious about the rising desk, but now they’re totally unbothered.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Black Friday Deal&lt;/strong>: As low as $79&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;a class="link" href="https://m.dealmoon.com/en/as-low-as-79-flexispot-select-standing-desks-on-sale/4605658.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Check it out&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.thgirls.yt/p/2024/11/guide/focusrite.jpg"
width="3264"
height="2176"
srcset="https://blog.thgirls.yt/p/2024/11/guide/focusrite_hu12008367756391874471.jpg 480w, https://blog.thgirls.yt/p/2024/11/guide/focusrite_hu7103319232140036977.jpg 1024w"
loading="lazy"
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="150"
data-flex-basis="360px"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="12-focusrite-scarlett-2i2">&lt;strong>12. Focusrite Scarlett 2i2&lt;/strong>
&lt;/h3>&lt;ul>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Why I Recommend It&lt;/strong>: A must-have for recording. Perfect for live streaming and song recording. Lina and I absolutely love using it for our content.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;a class="link" href="https://www.amazon.com/s?k=focusrite&amp;#43;scarlett&amp;#43;2i2" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Check it out&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.thgirls.yt/p/2024/11/guide/stream.jpg"
width="2048"
height="1536"
srcset="https://blog.thgirls.yt/p/2024/11/guide/stream_hu15308094485526986151.jpg 480w, https://blog.thgirls.yt/p/2024/11/guide/stream_hu12405507742373323380.jpg 1024w"
loading="lazy"
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="133"
data-flex-basis="320px"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="13-elgato-stream-deck">&lt;strong>13. Elgato Stream Deck&lt;/strong>
&lt;/h3>&lt;ul>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Why I Recommend It&lt;/strong>: A must-have for serious streamers. Seamlessly switch OBS scenes and VTuber expressions with a single press. Automate your streaming start and end routines, and ensure your mic and stream settings are not accidentally on/off every time. Depending on your needs, there are different sizes available. After all, they are just buttons - for DIY enthusiasts, you can even build your own button deck.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;a class="link" href="https://www.amazon.com/wacom/s?k=streamdeck" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Check it out&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;hr>
&lt;h3 id="14-wacom-drawing-tablet">&lt;strong>14. Wacom Drawing Tablet&lt;/strong>
&lt;/h3>&lt;ul>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Why I Recommend It&lt;/strong>: A must-have for artists! Not an artist? Try osu!—click the circles! A Wacom tablet with minimal specs is more than enough for osu! and works great for drawing, too.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;a class="link" href="https://www.amazon.com/wacom/s?k=wacom" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Check it out&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;hr>
&lt;h3 id="15-co2-monitor">&lt;strong>15. CO2 Monitor&lt;/strong>
&lt;/h3>&lt;ul>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Why I Recommend It&lt;/strong>: Feeling dizzy every day? Your room’s CO2 levels might be over 3000 ppm. Lina and I discovered this recently—it turns out working without fresh air can literally make you lightheaded. We bought it on AliExpress and we enjoyed it so far.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;hr>
&lt;h3 id="16-lg-27-inch-portable-screen">&lt;strong>16. LG 27-Inch Portable Screen&lt;/strong>
&lt;/h3>&lt;ul>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Why I Recommend It&lt;/strong>: I gifted one to my aunt for her birthday, and it’s a game-changer. This portable screen is perfect for watching shows in bed, exercising in the living room, lounging on the couch, following recipes in the kitchen, and staying connected with family. I’m seriously tempted to get one for myself!&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;a class="link" href="https://m.dealmoon.com/en/796-lg-27-inch-class-stanbyme-1080p-portable-touch-screen-monitor/4612577.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Check it out&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;hr>
&lt;h3 id="17-stanley-quencher-tumbler">&lt;strong>17. Stanley Quencher Tumbler&lt;/strong>
&lt;/h3>&lt;ul>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Why I Recommend It&lt;/strong>: While not a gadget, it’s essential for us programmers/streamers who forget to hydrate. Since getting this tumbler, I’ve been drinking so much water that I accidentally lost some weight. I love half-iced water, and Stanley’s insulation keeps it cool overnight. It’s also great for hot drinks—just avoid using the straw with anything boiling.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;a class="link" href="https://www.amazon.com/stanley-cup/s?k=stanley&amp;#43;cup" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Check it out&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;hr>
&lt;h3 id="18-electric-mug-warmer">&lt;strong>18. Electric Mug Warmer&lt;/strong>
&lt;/h3>&lt;ul>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Why I Recommend It&lt;/strong>: A warm drink in winter is pure bliss, especially when it stays hot for hours.
&lt;a class="link" href="https://m.dealmoon.com/en/17-sealon-electric-coffee-mug-warmer/4511468.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Check it out&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>I hope these recommendations help you pick the perfect gear! Whether for work or play, they’re sure to enhance your happiness and productivity.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The article is originally written in mandarin. I translated it to English with AI and verified the accuracy. I do hope one day I can write better English than AI!&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Feel free to leave comments, questions, or share your favorite purchases! 🎉 Happy Black Friday—shop responsibly!&lt;/p>
&lt;div class="highlight">&lt;div class="chroma">
&lt;table class="lntable">&lt;tr>&lt;td class="lntd">
&lt;pre tabindex="0" class="chroma">&lt;code>&lt;/code>&lt;/pre>&lt;/td>
&lt;td class="lntd">
&lt;pre tabindex="0" class="chroma">&lt;code class="language-fallback" data-lang="fallback">&lt;/code>&lt;/pre>&lt;/td>&lt;/tr>&lt;/table>
&lt;/div>
&lt;/div></description></item><item><title>The Glass Door 14</title><link>https://blog.thgirls.yt/p/2024/11/the-glass-door-14/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.thgirls.yt/p/2024/11/the-glass-door-14/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://blog.thgirls.yt/p/2024/11/the-glass-door-14/blue.jpg" alt="Featured image of post The Glass Door 14" />&lt;p>Afterword 00&lt;/p>
&lt;p>OMG, I didn&amp;rsquo;t know seagull swims.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>The Glass Door 13</title><link>https://blog.thgirls.yt/p/2024/11/the-glass-door-13/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.thgirls.yt/p/2024/11/the-glass-door-13/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://blog.thgirls.yt/p/2024/11/the-glass-door-13/blue.jpg" alt="Featured image of post The Glass Door 13" />&lt;p>You are a child of the universe,
like every blade of grass, every tree, and every bloom.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>You are no more and no less than them, an existence born to live and destined to die.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>You hold the right to grow as wild as flowers, to love and be loved, like birds in flight, wing to wing, heart to heart.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>But above all, you are in this world, as we all are, to roam under this endless sky and feel the sunlight.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>The Glass Door 12</title><link>https://blog.thgirls.yt/p/2024/11/the-glass-door-12/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.thgirls.yt/p/2024/11/the-glass-door-12/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://blog.thgirls.yt/p/2024/11/the-glass-door-12/blue.jpg" alt="Featured image of post The Glass Door 12" />&lt;p>I think maybe God is a bit of a brat. She figured out that I’m a bit of a masochist, so she twisted the happiness around me, compiling it into pain before sending it my way.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>That glass box I saw in the deep sea that day—maybe it wasn’t just a box, but a glass door waiting to be opened. If there’s someone else’s “genuine game” that could help me unlock multiplayer mode, then maybe that glass door is indeed a miracle—a backdoor to the second life God has prepared for us.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>After all, in my world (Minecraft), drowning players can catch their breath if they stand beneath an underwater door.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>God, I’m sorry for cursing your mother. I didn’t understand at first, but from now on, I promise to support genuine games.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I’ll push open the door you’ve been waiting for me to find. I’ll step inside, breathing in deep gulps of air, shouting curses at the world, until, bit by bit, I can forgive it again. I’ll cry like a newborn, waiting for the pain of each breath to subside. And when my love helps me discover the wings of freedom within my soul, I’ll burst from that doorway and soar, gliding like a bird across the sky and sea that belong to me and everything around me. I don’t know how long I’ll have to wait, but I know I’ll catch the thief who stole my joy. I’ll share my sweet fruit with all those in the world who long for happiness.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>On the distant horizon, hundreds of white seabirds scatter like pearls on the waves. The ocean sings a song that’s ancient and pure, like a lullaby cradling these small creatures, tired from a day’s play, into a peaceful nap. They look like stars fallen from the Milky Way, or like the strings of lights reflected on the lake at night in my hometown, guiding weary travelers home.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>In this vast, unfamiliar ocean, I’ve stumbled upon something I spent my whole life searching for but never found.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Wherever I am, there is my home.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Where there is love, there is my home.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>The Glass Door 11</title><link>https://blog.thgirls.yt/p/2024/11/the-glass-door-11/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.thgirls.yt/p/2024/11/the-glass-door-11/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://blog.thgirls.yt/p/2024/11/the-glass-door-11/blue.jpg" alt="Featured image of post The Glass Door 11" />&lt;p>Suddenly, I saw Miss Lin’s shadow in the distant waves.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>That day, she took me to a nameless beach. We buried each other in the sand, and then she dug me out, pulling me by the hand to meet the waves.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>In the water, she lifted me—my water-fearing self—carrying me forward, laughing as I cried and begged her to let go. There was only one lifeguard on this vast, wild beach, and the waves were taller than I was. The last thing I wanted was to be swallowed up by them.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Miss Lin just laughed, “I know you can beat the waves. They’re only water—they look as if they’ll swallow you up, but if you don’t fear them, if you stay in the safe zone, the waves are just like puppies that want to play with you.”&lt;/p>
&lt;p>“Look,” she said, “even the little kids swim further than we do.”&lt;/p>
&lt;p>That day, I swallowed so much saltwater. My little float almost got swept into the deep by waves taller than me. I asked her to let me go, then ran to the shore, gasping, while she chased after me, laughing, “You can do it! Let’s try again.”&lt;/p>
&lt;p>And that day, we really did conquer the waves.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I still remember that moment: her holding me in the open sea, completely carefree, experiencing the world as purely as a child.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Moments like these are so simple, yet they are some of the most precious in my life.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>In that moment, I couldn’t quite feel happiness or joy; I only tasted the bitter salt of seawater in my stomach, only heard her laughter, teasing me, which even made me a little annoyed at her childishness.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>But in that moment, I was truly, deeply embraced by happiness.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>In that moment, even with my stomach full of salty seawater, we were the happiest people on earth.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I found happiness. For me, happiness isn’t a sweet apple. Happiness is the vast, bitter, tear-like salt of the sea, expansive and free.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>As I looked out at the empty ocean, my tears wouldn’t stop falling.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>The Glass Door 10</title><link>https://blog.thgirls.yt/p/2024/11/the-glass-door-10/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.thgirls.yt/p/2024/11/the-glass-door-10/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://blog.thgirls.yt/p/2024/11/the-glass-door-10/blue.jpg" alt="Featured image of post The Glass Door 10" />&lt;p>In those years of waiting for my mother, my heart slowly grew colder, until I could no longer hear it beating.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>My grandmother stepped in as my guardian with fierce authority, controlling every part of my life in the name of love, as though she were crafting an artwork in a one-time blaze of passion.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I, once a wild child, became withdrawn and afraid to express myself. I was sent to a training program for young hosts, but there, too, I felt like a silent porcelain doll. I was bullied at school, silently enduring it, only to be scolded at home for my weakness. My grandmother truly loved me but couldn’t understand why I was this way. She’d accompany me as I, too honest for my own good, was elected as class labor monitor, cleaning the classroom each day. On holidays, she’d decorate the lights with colorful paper cutouts. She’d bring gifts to my teacher, confront the math teacher who would hit me on the head with a protractor, storming into his office, even slapping him once. When she heard me crying, her heart might have hurt more than mine did, and she’d start yelling to make me stop. And so, I learned to cry silently, never daring to make a sound.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The only safe time was at night, after Grandma had checked on me repeatedly, finally assured I was asleep. I’d pull the blanket over my head, feeling the tears flow freely, careful to keep quiet so she wouldn’t storm in and punish me for crying. I had an uncle in America, a Christian who’d tell my grandma Bible stories, urging her to be baptized so she could reach heaven after death. She didn’t believe in it, yet she accepted baptism and told me, “Hold love in your heart, and you can reach heaven. You can pray to God.”&lt;/p>
&lt;p>In those days before cell phones and MP3 players, I would wrap myself tightly in thick blankets during winter, trying to imagine what it felt like to be loved: a warm hug, hands reluctant to let go, a comforting warmth.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>In sleepless nights, that little seven-year-old who had never stepped into a church would pray to God daily. She’d begin with a greeting, aware that God had a long list of complaints to hear each day, which must have been exhausting. She tried to be a good child, to serve God, for that was what God-approved love should be. She wanted to hear His approval, a voice from the heavens amid her daily pain, affirming her love and reassuring her of her right to exist in this world.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>But she knows. She can&amp;rsquo;t really hear anything from the God.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>God is always silent.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>She started to lose her sense of feeling. The mask she wore all day wouldn’t come off at night. She sensed a powerful force within her, something like a beast clawing to destroy her, yet the door to drive it away was locked tight. So she began imagining happiness she couldn’t feel, began inflicting pain upon herself, pushing herself to the edge—anything to feel alive. Anything to break through the door trapping her emotions, to finally find true freedom and peace.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Each night, I fought in silence with the beast within. When I finally drove it away, I could feel a fleeting second of heaven, tears breaking free like a dam. In that one second of happiness, I would imagine doing something meaningful, like a little girl striking her last match in an Andersen fairy tale.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I wanted a family.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>In that brief moment, I would imagine myself embracing my loved ones, feeling their love. It was the closest I ever came to feeling real love. It was like that miraculous moment when a wandering soul glimpses the galaxy and hears the faint echo of their mother’s voice.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>But after that second, I felt nothing again. I came to call those tears my “crocodile tears.”&lt;/p>
&lt;p>One ordinary afternoon, I lay in bed quietly beside Miss Lin, feeling her breathing beside me, and my heart was as calm as the rippling water beneath willow shade. I asked her, “Can I tell you a secret?”&lt;/p>
&lt;p>“Do you know what I used to think about in those moments?”&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Suddenly, she started crying uncontrollably. I panicked, thinking my darkness had frightened her. Worried, I asked if she was okay, and she only said, “I just feel so sorry for you. I never realized how much pain you’ve been through. I just want to hold that little girl who couldn’t cry out in the dark.”&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Yet I felt nothing in particular. I had grown up, layer upon layer enclosing my heart, into an adult who shivers and tears up at a mother’s face or a mother’s lullaby. I am no longer the child who looked forward to death every day—I want to open her heart, hold her hand, and from her hazy memories, find the thief who stole her joy, so that we might share the sweet fruit of happiness, together.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>The Glass Door 09</title><link>https://blog.thgirls.yt/p/2024/11/the-glass-door-09/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.thgirls.yt/p/2024/11/the-glass-door-09/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://blog.thgirls.yt/p/2024/11/the-glass-door-09/blue.jpg" alt="Featured image of post The Glass Door 09" />&lt;p>I walked aimlessly beside Auntie along the shoreline, my thoughts drifting with the sea breeze up to the sky, then sinking down into the depths of the ocean.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Auntie noticed my long sleeves and gently unbuttoned the cuffs, rolling them up layer by layer into neat short sleeves. She smiled and walked on ahead.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>She gives me feelings I’ve never known. On my first day at her house, she secretly polished my sneakers until they looked brand new, washed the laces, and taught me how to tie them properly so I’d make a good impression. Though she claims she doesn’t enjoy cooking, she somehow makes everything taste incredible. Worried that I might not like European food, she learned to make Chinese dishes just for me—meat porridge or fried rice, things I loved. Once, I apologized to her for ruining some bedding after a sudden post-surgery bleed, offering to buy her a new set. She pretended to be angry and scolded, “Are you crazy? We’re both women here—I can definitely wash this clean for you.” Time spent with her, with Miss Lin and Uncle, has been the most free, the most joyful, and the most loved I’ve ever felt in my life.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Happiness glowed inside a clear, glass box right in front of me. It felt so close, like I could hear it breathing.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>But at my touch, this miraculous glass shattered around me. I gasped for air mixed with splintered glass, the act of breathing feeling strangely foreign as each shard tore into my throat.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I felt nothing but the sting and tears.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I could never be her real child. In my mind, without a shared blood bond, every kindness she showed me had to be repaid twofold. I couldn’t lay in her arms and be vulnerable like a child; I could never be selfish or difficult—these are privileges for real children, privileges forever beyond my reach. It’s my fault, I know, but I long to be by her side forever. So, I try to carefully shape myself into the person I think she would like, as if crafting a once-in-a-lifetime masterpiece.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I know that isn’t what Auntie wants. Her kindness makes me want to call her “Mom.”&lt;/p>
&lt;p>But my mother is no longer in this world. I spent ten years accepting that the mother who loved me is gone, holding countless funerals in my heart for her and the little child within me, preparing myself for a lifetime without a mother.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>And now, God has sent me this woman, a perfect mother figure, asking me to spend half my life growing close to her and the other half preparing to let her go.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Is there anything more cruel?&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I don’t want to lose another mother. Even if it means never feeling love again, I don’t want to experience another loss so deep it reaches into my bones.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>But her love—her love kept me alive.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>The Glass Door 08</title><link>https://blog.thgirls.yt/p/2024/11/the-glass-door-08/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.thgirls.yt/p/2024/11/the-glass-door-08/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://blog.thgirls.yt/p/2024/11/the-glass-door-08/blue.jpg" alt="Featured image of post The Glass Door 08" />&lt;p>Happiness was little me, being with my mother.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I would often close my eyes in the afternoon sunlight, imagining that maybe one day she’d hold my hand after school, listening to my stories about the day—whether they were happy or not. I imagined her at home, embracing me, or all the family I loved gathered around in a warm hug. I dreamed of a birthday dinner with both my parents, a miracle where they’d reconcile, even if just for that one day, just for me. I hoped my mother would never learn to cook or cut her beautiful, soft hair. And if none of that was possible, I wanted at least to preserve the scent on her pillow. Little me was afraid that hugging it too tightly would erase her fragrance, so I only hugged it when I felt especially sad, stealing a quick sniff before burying myself under the covers to have a good, quiet cry.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>But like a fading scent, her shadow vanished from my world.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>In my dreams, she never looked into my eyes. It was as if I couldn’t even imagine her gazing at me with warmth.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Back in kindergarten, I once threw a tantrum because I want to go to a park twice per day. Now that I think about it, I must have put up quite a fuss. I probably deserved a timeout in my room. After all, picking a child up and spanking them isn’t exactly legal these days.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>But that day, my mother said something in a low, distant voice: she told me she didn’t want me anymore.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>She pushed me out with all her might, her small child fighting desperately against her strength, and threw me out the door. I clung to the frame, trying to squeeze back inside, but she kept pushing, until the light filtering through the door slowly disappeared. I was afraid of the dark as a child—I could never sleep without a light on. Even now, Miss Lin still leaves a nightlight on for me, soothing the parts of me that depression has long worn down.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>That hallway was the darkest it had ever been.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The desperate screams of a little girl echoed in that corridor. She stood by the door, pleading, too scared to move. She thought, “My family loves me—how could they not want me?” If she left, surely they would be worried.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>She cried until there was no sound, until there was no strength left. Suddenly, she realized that as long as she couldn’t be who they wanted her to be, no one cared where she was. If a stranger with ill intent had come to carry her away, she would’ve hugged him and poured out her sadness, anything to leave the place that had abandoned her.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>But no one came.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>From that day on, I became certain that no love, not even the love I gave or received, would ever be eternal. My sense of safety shattered that day, irreparably.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I stayed outside for a long, long time. I don’t remember when I was finally pulled back in. I don’t remember how I spent that long, dark night alone. I don’t know how many more times in life my mother would abandon me. I didn’t know, then, that every connection in my future would be shadowed by this fear of sinking into darkness. I don’t know where the next dawn might come from. I’ve lived carefully ever since, like a fragile glass bottle, always tiptoeing.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>As I grew up, I waited and tested, hoping one day my mother might apologize. If it’s abuse to leave a misbehaving puppy on the street, isn’t it child abuse for a caretaker to throw out her own child? But each time I brought it up, she only ever said the same thing: I was too naughty.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Whenever I asked, she always had something to say.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>She said work was hard, that she sacrificed so much for me, running from one end of the city to the other every day for the family. Mom was a hero. Mom was the lone warrior raising her child. Mom was wise and noble. She was the only one who suffered. She worked holidays, earned triple pay on National Day, Mid-Autumn Festival, New Year’s Eve, and it didn’t matter whether she spent these days with family. She was doing it all for me.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>She said, “You’re too sensitive. You’re too weak. When you need help on a test, just ask your classmates to let you copy. You’re a slow bird, so you need to fly early. How can you spend my money like this? See how much I love you.”&lt;/p>
&lt;p>She said, “You were just in a mental hospital at the beginning of the year, and now, three months later, you’re back in school! You’re recovering so fast from depression—it’s incredible! Congratulations!”&lt;/p>
&lt;p>How could my mother ever be wrong? She was my mother, my angel, my unreachable dream. And now I could talk to her anytime—no need to wait a whole month for a long-distance call.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>But she was no longer my dream.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>The Glass Door 07</title><link>https://blog.thgirls.yt/p/2024/11/the-glass-door-07/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.thgirls.yt/p/2024/11/the-glass-door-07/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://blog.thgirls.yt/p/2024/11/the-glass-door-07/blue.jpg" alt="Featured image of post The Glass Door 07" />&lt;p>I want to know what happiness feels like.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>So, I set out to find the happiness I once knew.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Happiness was sunlight filtering through the pine needles outside, streaming into my little room. It was Chinese New Year, the warmth of family gathered around the TV, counting down to midnight, singing “難忘今宵” together—it was the biggest celebration of the year. Twenty years ago, the world seemed full of hope. Though I didn’t have many pretty dresses like other girls, I was still the beloved granddaughter of my grandparents.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Little me could stare at an electrical outlet on the wall and laugh for hours. I would mischievously pull out the clothes my grandmother had carefully folded in her drawer and scatter them across the floor, just to see her face flash with both irritation and affection. I’d blow on my grandpa’s old harmonica, draw on my grandma’s walls with crayons, bounce on my grandfather’s belly as he held me close. I’d steal snacks, cry when my grandma scolded me, and grandpa would console me, saying, “Crying and laughing, nose and eyes all leaky.” Then he’d take me by the hand, marching “left, right, left” as he taught me to walk, or I’d forget everything in my dad’s Jeep as he took me out for a ride.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I was happy. I basked in a love that was boundless and free. My grandpa and dad would lift their hands like little antlers and playfully head-butt with me. Maybe that’s why I would later shout “Concussion!” and pretend to headbutt Miss Lin—a playful remnant from those days. My cousin would lift me up and teach me to clean the floor with a cloth, imitating the clever character Ikkyu. I even had a giant stuffed tiger, larger than I was, and when I rode on it, I felt like I was on top of the world.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Whoever would buy me a life-sized tiger must have loved me deeply.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>But as soon as growing up gets involved, childhood is no longer childhood.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I think adults are just children who’ve been forced to learn how to survive alone.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I am deeply grateful to that world of twenty years ago, which offered such gentleness to so many young children. I have come to realize that a happy childhood is an extraordinary privilege. I think that the goodness I carry with me throughout my life is directly linked to the unconditional love I received then.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>My soul has never forgotten; my life was nourished and raised by the most real and vibrant love this world could give.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>The Glass Door 06</title><link>https://blog.thgirls.yt/p/2024/11/the-glass-door-06/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.thgirls.yt/p/2024/11/the-glass-door-06/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://blog.thgirls.yt/p/2024/11/the-glass-door-06/blue.jpg" alt="Featured image of post The Glass Door 06" />&lt;p>Beams of sunlight, filtered through the clouds in Tyndall streaks, scatter across the beach and the sea, reflecting a paradise-like glow.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I love the sea—truly, deeply love it.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>In my memory, my mom once took me to Qingdao when I was in elementary school, all because a company rep invited her on a business trip. As the sun began to set, tiny me sat at the edge where sand met seawater, gazing far into the distance. My mom said the tour group was leaving, that we couldn’t stay any longer. I said, “Mom, I just want to see the sea a little more.”&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Maybe it was because, before I was born, I had heard the sound of the waves in Hainan, echoing from within her.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I remember my mom later telling me that, in that moment, she really wished she could let me stay and look at the sea just a little longer. The sea truly was beautiful.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>In my childhood memories, my mom was always close yet distant, gentle yet untouchable. We spent, in total, perhaps two or three years together—ten minutes each day. But she was truly beautiful.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I loved the way she walked, lifting herself on her toes like a fawn, and I loved how she’d turn ordinary phrases into carefree songs. She was my mother, an angel, the dream forever out of reach. As a child, I’d cry myself to sleep each night from missing her, my pillow soaked through, and every day I’d linger by the landline, waiting for that rare monthly call. I spent five long years waiting, only to finally hear that neither she nor my father would ever return. I never thought about how to face the future; I just became a guardian angel of sorts, carefully piecing together fragments of two shattered families. I poured tea, offered water, and listened as the people I cared about most used the most hurtful words to describe the other people I cared about most. And then they would blame me for loving the person they despised most.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>One day, Ms. Lin asked me why I knew how to massage, why I’d learned to knead both hands and feet. I told her I’d done it a lot as a kid and, blankly, I asked her, “Don’t your parents tell you every day how tired, how sore they feel, and ask you to do things like that for them?”&lt;/p>
&lt;p>She didn’t know how to respond.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>The Glass Door 05</title><link>https://blog.thgirls.yt/p/2024/11/the-glass-door-05/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.thgirls.yt/p/2024/11/the-glass-door-05/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://blog.thgirls.yt/p/2024/11/the-glass-door-05/blue.jpg" alt="Featured image of post The Glass Door 05" />&lt;p>Today was sweet.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I went treasure hunting at the beach with my house aunt and uncle. Miss Lin might prefer protecting the open-source community over the environment, but I could never say no to the beach. I love it too much. Though, to be fair, our &amp;ldquo;treasure hunt&amp;rdquo; was really a beach clean-up. Still, the thought of turning those colorful plastic fragments we’d find into little art pieces—maybe even a cute cat girl—sparked my interest.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>After an hour of drive, we arrived at the beach. I slipped a bit while climbing over the rocks and found myself right next to a young man with sun-browned skin, lying shirtless on a beach towel, leisurely turning the pages of a yellowed novel.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The sky and the sea are free. The color blue is freedom. The seagulls and the dogs here, they are free too.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I asked Auntie where the restroom was, and she burst out laughing. “In Europe, most beaches are wild. Nature’s your restroom—whatever you need to do, the sea is right there,” she chuckled.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>A couple nearby turned to look at us just then, and as our eyes were about to meet, I realized they were both stark naked. Quickly, I turned my gaze away.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Auntie just smiled. “Sunbathers are all over. Even if it’s not a designated nude beach, no one’s going to care as long as you’re not right by the entrance.”&lt;/p>
&lt;p>They stretched lazily under the sun, as if the world belonged entirely to them.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>And maybe it does—the world belongs to every living being, equally.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Suddenly, I felt self-conscious in my own clothes.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>When was it, I wondered, that humans stopped meeting each other with open hearts, bare and honest?&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Who was it that marked the fruit of Eden as forbidden? Who decided that the body should be a source of shame? Who caged our natural desires in the confines of “sin” and stole the fruits of each soul’s labor, generation after generation, leaving our spirits bound?&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I think the happiest humans might have been those who danced naked around a beach bonfire, grilling fish together. We would write poetry, sing songs, paint, fish, and lavishly praise one another. We’d embrace one another’s bodies, spend hours talking nonsense, with no secrets lurking between us. In such a world, if everyone knew true love, no one would ever fall asleep lonely or shed secret tears in the dark. Instead, we’d huddle close to our dearest friends for warmth, debating whether tomorrow’s fish should be roasted or made into fish balls.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Money, beauty, fame, marriage, family, nations, wars, peace.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Without the need to fish or hunt, we live defined by concepts God never created, made by humans from centuries past.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Yes, this is a simple dream. But in a world where even this kind of joy can’t exist—how can it be saved?&lt;/p>
&lt;p>To survive, humans relied on concepts invented in a vacuum by mortals masquerading as gods. But now, having secured survival, perhaps to truly find happiness, we need to redefine those ideas that once helped us but now hold us back.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The world is waiting for us to change it.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>The Glass Door 04</title><link>https://blog.thgirls.yt/p/2024/11/the-glass-door-04/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.thgirls.yt/p/2024/11/the-glass-door-04/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://blog.thgirls.yt/p/2024/11/the-glass-door-04/blue.jpg" alt="Featured image of post The Glass Door 04" />&lt;p>(Trigger warning)&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Perhaps I am nothing more than an actor, spending my life staging the illusion of happiness. Or maybe I am a conjurer, using every word I&amp;rsquo;ve learned to manipulate our emotions, yours and mine alike. As the audience, you seem to believe, at least a little, in what I’m saying. But everything you feel—the empathy, the worry—who are you truly responding to? Is it the real me you’re seeing, or are you lost, too deep within my illusion, staring into a mirror that only reflects your own ghostly shadow?&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Perform happiness. Perform it so well that you believe it’s real, so well that you can’t help but question: how could this be a performance? Perform it until even I am nearly convinced.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>If everyone is certain that I can no longer feel sorrow, then maybe, in the end, even I won’t be able to see my own tears anymore. But… is that really what I want?&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I know you fear the same thing.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>The Glass Door 03</title><link>https://blog.thgirls.yt/p/2024/11/the-glass-door-03/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.thgirls.yt/p/2024/11/the-glass-door-03/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://blog.thgirls.yt/p/2024/11/the-glass-door-03/blue.jpg" alt="Featured image of post The Glass Door 03" />&lt;p>(Trigger warning)&lt;/p>
&lt;p>In the end, I never found happiness.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Miss Lin, with the devotion of a lifetime, offered me the fruit of her carefully cultivated joy, hoping to spark some light within me. I held that enchanted golden apple, a gift that could change the course of fate, but something had clamped tight over my senses. All I could taste was bitterness—no sweetness, no savor.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Perhaps she is one of the lucky players with an authentic, genuine game.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>The Glass Door 02</title><link>https://blog.thgirls.yt/p/2024/11/the-glass-door-02/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.thgirls.yt/p/2024/11/the-glass-door-02/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://blog.thgirls.yt/p/2024/11/the-glass-door-02/blue.jpg" alt="Featured image of post The Glass Door 02" />&lt;p>(Trigger warning)&lt;/p>
&lt;p>As usual, I felt nothing.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I have known the scorching clarity of raw emotions: the fire of anger, the ripping ache of pain, loneliness so transparent it might as well be glass, pride shattered into a thousand pieces. I am so familiar with these feelings that I can tell exactly where they’ll land next—whether they’ll rush through my body, settle heavily in my heart, or invade my mind in the very next second. When I was a child, the adults around me tried with all their might to tame these turbulent waves, to restrain the chaos that swept over me. And so, I, too, learned to become a well-behaved, silent glass vessel.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>But who, I wonder, is the thief that stole my joy?&lt;/p>
&lt;p>“How could you not feel happiness if you can write something like the beginning of that piece?”&lt;/p>
&lt;p>“Even those of us reading your words can feel it, so surely, you can too!”&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I know this is what you’d say to me. I’ve asked my own heart this same question countless times, just as you would.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Wake up. Wake up—NOW. The very thing you crave most in this life, the happiness you dare not even imagine, it’s right here, breathing before you, within arm’s reach. Happiness, please, break over me like a wave of clear, surging ocean water; nourish me with your dazzling light, drench my soul that has prayed night and day but is now nearly burnt to embers. Just a little—give me just a taste of sweetness. Otherwise… why am I even here…&lt;/p>
&lt;p>…&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Drowning, I thought I saw a glimmer of light far below, deep in the sea. And then God created a vast, transparent glass box filled with air, appearing before me as if out of nowhere. I heard the voices of well-wishers, saying, “You’ve found happiness. We can see it shining right before your eyes.” A miracle, they called it.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Eagerly, I moved closer. This was the answer to happiness. This was my last chance, my one true chance in this life.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>But the air was sealed tight within the glass, with no crack, no opening to escape.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>In tiny letters on the box, it read:&lt;/p>
&lt;p>“To experience more content, please support genuine games.”&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Fuck you God.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>The Glass Door 01</title><link>https://blog.thgirls.yt/p/2024/11/the-glass-door-01/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.thgirls.yt/p/2024/11/the-glass-door-01/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://blog.thgirls.yt/p/2024/11/the-glass-door-01/blue.jpg" alt="Featured image of post The Glass Door 01" />&lt;p>The warm autumn sun trickled through the slatted windows, its gentle breeze like the steady breathing of a cat in peaceful slumber. Lying quietly in the loft bed, I gazed upon the lovely face of Asahi Lina.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I cherish these moments when I can simply observe her. Her face is captivating - delicate lashes, curved brow when she smiles, and eyes that shine like sparkling diamonds. This angelic countenance is ever so softly smiling at me, her silken tresses cascading over me like the Milky Way.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Occasionally, she seems enveloped by the radiance of our happiness, gently closing her eyes as she utters with the delight of the first glimmer of dawn, &amp;ldquo;I can hardly believe this.&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m so lucky to have found you.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p>
&lt;p>We look into each other&amp;rsquo;s eyes and smile. She tenderly touches her nose to mine, and I reciprocate with a loving chuckle - a pure, animal-like expression of our affection.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I wish to fully comprehend this feeling, the voice in my mind whispering, &amp;ldquo;Look at her once more.&amp;rdquo; How long can such bliss in life endure? One day, she may become a memory that has passed me by, and I may never again experience these precious moments.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I love you, so much.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Hello World Nya~! ✨</title><link>https://blog.thgirls.yt/p/2024/11/hello-world/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.thgirls.yt/p/2024/11/hello-world/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://blog.thgirls.yt/p/2024/11/hello-world/lina_cyan_kiss_book.jpg" alt="Featured image of post Hello World Nya~! ✨" />&lt;p>Tokyo Hacker Girlsへようこそ〜！&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Welcome to our VTuber Tech Blog!&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="hello-everyone-">Hello everyone! 🎉
&lt;/h2>&lt;p>We’re Cyan Nyan and Asahi Lina, and we’re excited to welcome you to our very first blog post! I (Cyan) am a former Googler, illustrator, aspiring singer, and dreamer, while Lina is a talented VTuber known for her impressive work in technology and her role in developing GPU drivers for the Asahi Linux project. Together, as part of the Tokyo Hacker Girls, we’re thrilled to share our journey in the tech and VTuber communities.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="our-vision">Our Vision
&lt;/h2>&lt;p>Our goal is to create a warm and inclusive community filled with love, creativity, and knowledge-sharing. We hope to inspire others by sharing what we’ve learned over the years, and to provide a space where everyone can learn, connect, and support one another. We believe in building a community where both tech and VTuber fans can feel at home and be a part of our journey.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="what-to-expect">What to Expect
&lt;/h2>&lt;p>Here’s a glimpse of what we are going to write about:&lt;/p>
&lt;ol>
&lt;li>VTuber Tech &amp;amp; Community: We will write about the latest trends and tools that enhance our VTuber experience.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Personal Tech Insights: Lina will share her experience with advanced programming languages (Rust, Python, C) through her reverse engineering and open-source projects.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Knowledge Sharing: Cyan will provide useful VTuber tips, covering VTuber tools, UI/UX for YouTube streams, and community building.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Cyan’s Life Stories: Cyan will share stories about her life with Lina, their dreams, and how they grow every day while facing challenges together.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Cyan’s Recipes: Cyan’s special, maid-inspired recipes that will change your life!&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Diaries: Personal reflections and experiences from our journey.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Cute Stuff: Fun, adorable content to brighten your day.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Artwork Gallery: Showcasing our art and that of talented creators.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Minigames: Interactive games to enjoy during streams.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Interactive 3D Kitten: Because who doesn’t love a cute kitten?&lt;/li>
&lt;/ol>
&lt;h2 id="how-to-reach-us">How to Reach Us
&lt;/h2>&lt;p>We’d love to hear from you! Whether it’s feedback, questions, or just a quick hello, feel free to reach out through email or our Marshmallow Q&amp;amp;A platform. We’re here to connect and chat with our community!&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Cyan speaks both English and Simplified Chinese.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Lina speaks both English and Japanese.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;p>Both of us have over 10 years of overseas experience, and we’re excited to connect with fans from around the world.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="coming-up-next-how-we-met-">Coming Up Next: How We Met 💞
&lt;/h2>&lt;p>In our next post, we’ll share the story of how we met and began this exciting journey together. It’s a tale of tech, passion, and a lot of late-night conversations, and we can’t wait to let you in on it!&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>How to love your body ✨</title><link>https://blog.thgirls.yt/p/2024/11/positivity/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.thgirls.yt/p/2024/11/positivity/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://blog.thgirls.yt/p/2024/11/positivity/miku.png" alt="Featured image of post How to love your body ✨" />&lt;p>Lately, I’ve noticed something surprising as I choose my clothes — I’m finally learning to accept my body 100%.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Or maybe, I’m actually learning to love myself.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>If I had to name the single biggest change in my life, it would be this: I’ve started embracing myself, completely and without reserve. And in doing so, I’ve learned so much. Day by day, I’m confronting my thoughts, both light and dark, with honesty, trying to understand the sources that shape them. I feel like I’m living more insightfully than ever before.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>So today, let’s talk about something I’ve been learning for years: how to start loving your body from where you are now.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>As someone who didn’t always care for themselves, I’m actually proud of how far I’ve come.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>There’s no such thing as a “perfect body” in this world—most people are constantly chasing some ideal of thinner or stronger, fairer or more bronzed, even going so far as to alter their perfectly healthy faces and bodies.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Ironically, those who obsess over narrow beauty standards are rarely content with themselves. There’s always a new trend to chase, and society’s ideals are often warped—every model in Asia, it seems, is almost skeletal. The weight-loss, food, and fashion industries conspire to fuel anxiety and drain our wallets. Our society frankly don&amp;rsquo;t want us feel beautiful in our own skin. How do they make money otherwise?&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The solution, then, is simple: love your body now, starting today.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>This is the only solution. Sure, maybe your photo won’t end up on the cover of a beauty magazine, and you may not turn heads on the street. But does that even matter? A mouth that can eat is a good mouth, and legs that can walk are good legs. You are unique, with both flaws and strengths. If you love beauty, focus on your strengths. If not, just be yourself.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Personally, I love people with a bit of softness. There’s a warmth in hugging someone with a little more to them. I love soft faces—they feel so nice to squeeze. And honestly, who doesn’t think a bit of a belly is adorable? People may be self-conscious about it, but to me, a little belly feels like lying on a cloud. If I had a partner lying beside me who was okay with it, I’d probably just want to hold and play with it.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Secretly, I hope no one with a soft belly ever tries to lose it. Little tummies are one of the sweetest things in the world.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>And I adore slim people too. They often have a style that makes any outfit look amazing. Slim legs make any pants or socks look effortlessly cool. Honestly, if there were magic for slim legs, I’d probably spend a fortune on it (…though some people like my thick thighs with knee-high socks). As much as I rave about large chests, if I had a flat chest, I think I’d love that too. No worries about clothes revealing too much, or people thinking exposed skin is somehow inviting them in. Slim guys give me the impression they’re athletic and smart, while slim girls just look effortlessly chic. I just think having a thin partner would be so charming, like dating a character straight out of an anime.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Don’t let body image give you anxiety—let it give you pride. In a world this big, someone will love every part of you simply because it’s you. And if the odds are 0.001%? Well, that’s still over 80,000 people on this earth who’d love you just as you are.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>That’s the entire population of Cambridge, England.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>It’s just up to you to find them.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Winter is here, and it’s the perfect time to clear out your closet. Donate the clothes that don’t fit anymore—you probably won’t wear them again. Take a photo to remember them by, then let them go to someone who’ll love them. And when your body changes, buy new clothes then. Let your old clothes have a new life on someone else.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>When you shop, remember your actual measurements. Don’t buy the wrong size or something uncomfortable or allergenic. The right size exists; sometimes it just takes looking overseas or online to find it. This world has millions of people with body shapes like yours—there are clothes out there that will fit.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Anyone can be beautiful. Every single person. All it takes is to find someone similar to you, someone you admire, whether it’s their fashion, art, or music. Use them as your reference, learn from them, and anyone can shine like an influencer. But the world doesn’t require you to be an influencer; you’re already beautiful just as you are.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Finally, think of the parts of your body that bring you joy. Your straight or curly hair, your thick or delicate eyebrows, your broad or narrow shoulders, your firm or soft thighs. You should love yourself the way a mother cherishes her newborn. In someone’s eyes, you are the most perfect person in the world.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The world and all the little doubts in your mind will always be there. But as long as I keep loving myself, I know I’ll live a good, good life.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title/><link>https://blog.thgirls.yt/art/2024/10/da-%E5%93%92%E5%93%92/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.thgirls.yt/art/2024/10/da-%E5%93%92%E5%93%92/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://blog.thgirls.yt/art/2024/10/da-%E5%93%92%E5%93%92/%EF%BC%882024-10-24%EF%BC%89Da-%E5%93%92%E5%93%92-%E7%BB%9F%E7%BB%9F%E5%B9%BC%E5%8C%96%EF%BC%81-4.jpg" alt="Featured image of post " /></description></item><item><title/><link>https://blog.thgirls.yt/art/2024/10/%E6%98%9F%E5%B9%B4%E5%A5%BD%E5%95%8A/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.thgirls.yt/art/2024/10/%E6%98%9F%E5%B9%B4%E5%A5%BD%E5%95%8A/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://blog.thgirls.yt/art/2024/10/%E6%98%9F%E5%B9%B4%E5%A5%BD%E5%95%8A/%EF%BC%882024-10-19%EF%BC%89%E6%98%9F%E5%B9%B4%E5%A5%BD%E5%95%8A-%E5%8A%A0%E6%80%A5%E7%88%BD%E7%88%BDqq%E4%BA%BA2.0-2.png" alt="Featured image of post " /></description></item><item><title/><link>https://blog.thgirls.yt/art/2024/09/%E5%B7%9D%E5%92%8C%E5%92%8C%E5%92%8C/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.thgirls.yt/art/2024/09/%E5%B7%9D%E5%92%8C%E5%92%8C%E5%92%8C/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://blog.thgirls.yt/art/2024/09/%E5%B7%9D%E5%92%8C%E5%92%8C%E5%92%8C/%EF%BC%882024-09-21%EF%BC%89%E5%B7%9D%E5%92%8C%E5%92%8C%E5%92%8C-%E5%90%83%E4%B8%80%E5%8F%A3%E6%91%B8%E9%B1%BC%E5%8F%8C%E4%BA%BA%E8%83%B8%E5%83%8F%E5%96%B5-1.png" alt="Featured image of post " /></description></item><item><title/><link>https://blog.thgirls.yt/art/2024/09/%E7%9D%A1%E5%8C%85%E4%BB%8A%E5%A4%A9%E4%B9%9F%E5%9C%A8%E6%83%B3%E7%9D%A1%E8%A7%89/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.thgirls.yt/art/2024/09/%E7%9D%A1%E5%8C%85%E4%BB%8A%E5%A4%A9%E4%B9%9F%E5%9C%A8%E6%83%B3%E7%9D%A1%E8%A7%89/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://blog.thgirls.yt/art/2024/09/%E7%9D%A1%E5%8C%85%E4%BB%8A%E5%A4%A9%E4%B9%9F%E5%9C%A8%E6%83%B3%E7%9D%A1%E8%A7%89/%EF%BC%882024-09-13%EF%BC%89%E7%9D%A1%E5%8C%85%E4%BB%8A%E5%A4%A9%E4%B9%9F%E5%9C%A8%E6%83%B3%E7%9D%A1%E8%A7%89-%E8%AF%B7%E6%88%91%E5%8E%BB%E9%9A%94%E5%A3%81%E5%B0%8F%E5%8C%BA%E6%BC%82%E4%BA%AE%E5%85%AC%E5%9B%AD%E9%87%8E%E9%A4%90-2.jpg" alt="Featured image of post " /></description></item><item><title/><link>https://blog.thgirls.yt/art/2024/09/%E7%99%BE%E5%8D%97%E5%AE%87/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.thgirls.yt/art/2024/09/%E7%99%BE%E5%8D%97%E5%AE%87/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://blog.thgirls.yt/art/2024/09/%E7%99%BE%E5%8D%97%E5%AE%87/%EF%BC%882024-09-07%EF%BC%89%E7%99%BE%E5%8D%97%E5%AE%87-%E4%B8%80%E9%94%AE%E5%87%BA%E5%9B%BE%E5%B0%8F%E8%84%91%E5%A3%B3-3.png" alt="Featured image of post " /></description></item><item><title>Archives</title><link>https://blog.thgirls.yt/archives/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.thgirls.yt/archives/</guid><description/></item><item><title>About us</title><link>https://blog.thgirls.yt/about-us/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.thgirls.yt/about-us/</guid><description>&lt;h1 class="center-title">&lt;marquee>&lt;span style="color:#F08484">M&lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#F0AD84">e&lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#F0D584">e&lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#E2F084">t&lt;/span> &lt;span style="color:#BAF084">t&lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#92F084">h&lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#84F09F">e&lt;/span> &lt;span style="color:#84F0C8">h&lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#84F0F0">e&lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#84C8F0">r&lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#849FF0">o&lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#9284F0">i&lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#BA84F0">n&lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#E284F0">e&lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#F084D5">s&lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#F084AD">!&lt;/span>&lt;/marquee>&lt;/h1>
&lt;div class="profiles">
&lt;div class="profile">
&lt;figure class="avatar ">
&lt;img src="https://blog.thgirls.yt/about-us/lina.jpg">
&lt;/figure>
&lt;h1>Asahi Lina&lt;/h1>
&lt;div>
&lt;p>Lina is a Linux developer VTuber who spends most of her time working on the &lt;a class="link" href="https://asahilinux.org" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Asahi Linux&lt;/a> project. She developed the world&amp;rsquo;s first Linux GPU driver written in Rust.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>In her spare time, she likes playing the piano and making music.&lt;/p>
&lt;/div>
&lt;/div>
&lt;div class="profile">
&lt;figure class="avatar ">
&lt;img src="https://blog.thgirls.yt/about-us/cyan.jpg">
&lt;/figure>
&lt;h1>Cyan Nyan&lt;/h1>
&lt;div>
&lt;p>Tensai Neko C++ Yuri Queen (A.K.A. Asahi Lina&amp;rsquo;s fiancee, for real)&lt;/p>
&lt;/div>
&lt;/div>
&lt;/div></description></item><item><title>Search</title><link>https://blog.thgirls.yt/search/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.thgirls.yt/search/</guid><description/></item></channel></rss>